<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Parameterizations of Weibull Distribution</title>
      <link>/2017/11/09/parameterizations-of-weibull-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/09/parameterizations-of-weibull-distribution/</guid>
      <description>Most Widely Used Distribution in Reliability Engineering Weibull distribution is widely used because its flexibility and simplicity. It is the most widely used in the field of reliability engineering. Engineers use Weibull plot to find clues about whether the failure is infant mortality or wearing out, or use the curve shape to determine whether there are more than one underlying failure mechanisms. Actually, there are several software companies selling software packages named after the Swedish Engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repairable Systems and NHPP</title>
      <link>/2017/10/13/nhpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/13/nhpp/</guid>
      <description>Probabilistic Models for Repairable Systerms When analyzing repairable systems, areas of interest may include assessing the expected number of failures during the warranty period, maintaining a minimum mission reliability, evaluating the rate of wearout, determining when to replace or overhaul a system and minimizing life cycle costs.
When the downtime of the repairable systems are short, the point processes are often the model of choice. A point process gives:
 N(t): a counting function that keeps track of the cumulative number of failures a given system has had from time zero to time t.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>